&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以我们要做出反应，我们要实现代码
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So we're gonna take
a react out and we're gonna implement code
作为一个小组，作为一个团队，分裂和懒惰加载在一起。
splitting and lazy loading
together as a group, as a team.
我们会在行动中看到这一点，因为这是其中之一。
And we'll kinda see this in action,
because it is one of those things.
我对它有点着迷，因为我觉得看起来很难，所以
I'm kinda fascinated with it, because
I think it seems hard on the tin, so
每个人都避免它。
everybody avoids it.
我们不能在我们的应用程序中做到这一点，我想要点击的那种点
We couldn't do that in our app and
the kind of point that I wanna like hit on
就像你可以明天做这件事的某些部分。
like there are parts of this
that you can do like tomorrow.
在您的应用程序中，这将产生类似于戏剧性的影响
In your application that will
have like dramatic impact
在应用程序的加载时间。
on the load time of your application.
因此，在要点中有一个链接的存储库，称为NOTED和
So there is a repository linked
in the gist called noted and
我们带它去兜风。
we'll take it for a spin.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：每个人都有自己的默认应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Everyone
has their default app.
这就像一个笑话，每个框架都有一个待办事项列表。
It's like a like joke that every
framework has a to-do list.
我的事情是，我反复做降价编辑。
My thing is I make mark
down editors repeatedly.
很酷，所以这里我们有一个应用程序。
Cool, so here we have an application.
你有一些笔记在旁边，我出色的设计技巧。
You've got some notes over on the side
with my excellent design skills.
你可以稍后再称赞我。
You can compliment me on those later.
我们可以点击通过，就像你可以看到嘿，这是在渲染标记下来的注意事项。
We can click through like you can see hey,
here's the note in rendered mark down.
我们可以继续，我们可以编辑它，并且
We can go ahead and we can edit it, and
我们得到了这个漂亮的代码编辑器，就像我可以改变一些东西一样。
we get this nifty code editor like
where I can change some stuff.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我在下标预览和侧边栏中更改此功能。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I change this in
the mark down preview and in the sidebar.
非常酷，我可以关闭给定的注释并返回到最初的页面。
Very cool, I can close the given note and
go back to this initial page.
这就是整个应用程序。
That's the entire application.
有一件事我们可以看一下，让我们在这里做一个绩效审计
One thing we can take a look at,
let's do a performance audit here and
我会继续的。
I'll go ahead.
我会做开始分析并重新加载页面，
I'll do the start profiling and
reload the page,
这只会让你从头到尾都能得到最初的开始时间。
which will just get you that initial
start time all the way through.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：当它认为已经完成时，它会自动发出声音。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And it automatically
sounds when it thinks it is done.
所以我们发送这个大型名称.somegarbage.bundle.js，
So we send this large
named.somegarbage.bundle.js,
你可以看到我们花了相当多的钱
you can see that we
spend a decent amount of
解析它的时间比其他任何东西都要多。
time parsing it more than anything else.
但就像前面使用SendGrid中的示例一样，
But like using the example
from sendgrid earlier,
我甚至不知道他们是否会使用编辑器。
I don't even know if they're
going to use the editor.
这个应用程序没有太多可做的，但是
This application there's not a lot to do,
but
就像这是一个更大的应用程序的缩影版本。
like this is like a microcosm
version of a larger application.
我们不知道用户要做什么，所以如果我只是
We don't know what the user is going
to do, so it'd be great like if I only
发送给他们，就像代码编辑器一样，如果他们需要的话，它就在那边。
send them that like code editor that was
over on the side there if they need it.
给他们最初的页面，让他们互动，
To get them that initial page,
to get them interactive,
他们还没看纸条。
they're not looking at a note yet.
我还没有在这里做任何减价。
I'm not doing any markdown over here yet.
这就像原始文本字符串一样，我可以让它们达到
This is just like the raw string of text
like I can get them to the point where
他们之前已经在和页面互动了，他们还不需要那个东西。
they're interacting with the page before,
they don't need that thing yet.
就像当他们需要降价组件时，我们会把它发给他们。
Like when they need the mark down
component, we'll send it to them.
当他们需要编辑的时候，我们会发给他们。
When they need the editor,
we'll send it to them.
但为什么要让他们预先支付那个费用呢？
But why make them pay that cost upfront?
就像在更大的应用程序中一样，他们可能永远不需要它。
Like in a larger application,
they might never need it.
它们可能会转到应用程序的其他部分。
They might go to some other
part of the application.